atube.me 2014-11-22

# Privacy policy of this web site | aTube Catcher Official Web Site

**Privacy Policy**

Through our privacy policy we inform you about politics of safe usage data and how we protect the privacy of the visitors.

The use of this web site, implies full and unreserved acceptance of all of the provisions contained in this Legal Notice, so if you do not agree with any of the terms established herein shall not use and / or access this site.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. Your continued use of any portion of this site following notification or posting of such modifications will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

Cookies

This site uses cookies, which are small data files that are generated on your computer, which stores information without providing references to deduce personal information from this data.

You can configure your browser to notify and reject the storage of cookies sent by this site, without this affecting the ability to access the content. However, we are not responsible for the deactivation of these may affect your experience on the web site, like the posibility to share your comments, experiences with other users or be able to post in the forum.

Marks Web / Web Beacons

Like the cookies this site may also contain Web beacons, an electronic image that permits count the number of visitors, users to access the site or accessing certain cookies the same way, thus, we can provide a more personalized experience.

Actions of third parties

Also, you will find within this site, pages, promotions and microsites, surveys, sponsors, advertisers, partners, etc, together with other shared services, which this site may disclose information provided by you under your approval.

The information provided on these sites is subject to the privacy policies or legends of information that are deployed in such sites and is not subject to this privacy policy. We strongly recommend that the Members to review in detail the privacy policies that are deployed on the third party sites.

Privacy Policy Advertising provided at this site:

We studied the preferences of our users, their demographic characteristics, traffic patterns, and other information together to better understand who our audience are and what you need. The tracking of users' preferences also helps us serve you more relevant advertising.

Privacy Policy Tracking Sources Used In This Site:

**Personally identifiable information**  

Information collected

All the information entered into the aTube Catcher software is used only for the purposes for which the application was developed, therefore none information is collected, stored or transmitted by aTube Catcher to external servers, including URL's or search phrases. All the information related to the status of the application is stored into the End User computer, such information is untraceable and is not linked or related with personal information, and can be easily destroyed by the user with simply deleting the temporary files. 

Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you on our behalf when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including personal information such as your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  

Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.   

Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information when we ask for this information.  

Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to administer the site and to track users' movements around the site.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information except during special promotions such as free trials when subscription IP addresses are temporarily tied to personally identifiable information.   

Cookies

We use session ID cookies on this site to maintain your session active. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.  

Clear Gifs

We do employ this software technology called clear gifs that is used to manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  

Third Party Advertisers

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by a DsNET Corp. proprietary ad serving system. We share Web site usage information about users with reputable third party ad networks for the purpose of targeting our banners.

We use third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you on our behalf when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including personal information such as your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  

Links to Other Sites

aTube Catcher contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by its developers. Please be aware that we, aTube Catcher, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by aTube Catcher.

By visiting this Site, all visitors consent to the collection, maintenance, and processing of their personal and non-personal information outside the United States.  

Access to Personally Identifiable Information

We do no store personally identifiable information, therefore we don't maintain databases that can be accesed or modified with such kind of information.  

Security

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us online. On the aTube Catcher website fill the contact form.

**Policy on Personal Data Protection**

To use certain services or access certain content, like forum, web comments or polls, you must provide certain personal information, which will only be used for the purpose they were collected.

The type of information that he may be requested includes, but not limited to, your name, email address (e-mail), date of birth, sex, occupation, city and country of origin and personal interests, among others, not all information requested at the time to participate in the binding site is obligatory, except that we deem appropriate and so we let you know.

As a general principle, **this site will not share or disclose information except when authorized by you** or in the following cases:

> * When it is required by a competent authority and subject to the fulfillment of legal proceedings and related  
>  * When in the opinion of this site is necessary to enforce the terms of use and other terms of this page, or to safeguard the integrity of other users or the site.

And be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personal information online in a public area like the forum, comments page or chat, that information can be collected and used by others. We do not control the actions of our visitors.

Responsible behavior

All information provided must be true. For these purposes, you guarantee the authenticity of all data that communicates as a result of the completion of the necessary forms for subscription to the Services, access to content or restricted areas of the site. In any case you will be solely responsible for any false or inaccurate conduct and the damages caused to third parties in this site or the information provided.

You agree to act with responsibly at this site and to treat other visitors with respect.

Contact

If you have questions or concerns about this Policy, please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://atube-catcher.dsnetwb.com/get-video-software-windows-home/contact) at any time via the contact form available on site or via email

vailable on site or via email
